<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OpenStack on Feisky</title><link>https://feisky.xyz/tags/openstack/</link><description>Recent content in OpenStack on Feisky</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>zh-cn</language><atom:link href="https://feisky.xyz/tags/openstack/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Going Native with OpenStack Centric Applications: Murano</title><link>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-02-26-going-native-with-openstack-centric-applications-murano/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-02-26-going-native-with-openstack-centric-applications-murano/</guid><description>&lt;p>Following on our previous discussion surveying the projects supporting applications within OpenStack, let’s continue our review with an in-depth look at the OpenStack-native Application Catalog: Murano, currently an incubation status project, having seen its functionality and core services integration advanced over the past few OpenStack releases.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-is-it">What is it?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>An application catalog developed by Mirantis, HP and others (now including Cisco), that allows application developers and cloud administrators to publish applications in a categorized catalog to be perused and deployed by application consumers. The selection of applications available within the catalog is intended to be that of released versions (ready-state) of applications (cloud-native or enterprise-architected), not application versions that are mid-development. Ideally, these are applications ready to be consumed and run by application users.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How enable OpenStack allinone vm to access external network</title><link>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-03-02-how-enable-openstack-allinone-vm-to-access-external-network/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-03-02-how-enable-openstack-allinone-vm-to-access-external-network/</guid><description>&lt;p>首先需要为OpenStack添加一个公网网络，假设All-in-one环境建的公网网段为10.10.10.0/24，公网网关为10.10.10.1。这样为虚拟机绑定公网IP后，由于网关是不存在的，虚拟机无法访问外网。那虚拟机如果想访问外网怎么办呢？&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Integrating Openstack and Kubernetes with Murano</title><link>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-02-26-integrating-openstack-and-kubernetes-with-murano/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-02-26-integrating-openstack-and-kubernetes-with-murano/</guid><description>&lt;p>There’s a perceived competition between OpenStack and containers such as Docker, but in reality, the two technologies are a powerful combination. They both solve similar problems, but on different layers of the stack, so combining the two can give users more scalability and automation than ever before.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That containers app you wrote needs to run somewhere. This is particularly true for orchestrated container applications, such as those managed by Kubernetes. What’s more, if your application is complicated enough that it needs to scale up and down, you need to be running it in an environment that can, itself, scale up and down. This is where OpenStack comes in.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>OpenStack Magnum社区及项目介绍</title><link>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-06-24-openstack-magnum/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://feisky.xyz/posts/2015-06-24-openstack-magnum/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;img src="https://feisky.xyz/images/magnum.png" alt="">&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Add network management for native docker &lt;a href="https://blueprints.launchpad.net/magnum/+spec/native-docker-network">https://blueprints.launchpad.net/magnum/+spec/native-docker-network&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;a href="https://etherpad.openstack.org/p/magnum-native-docker-network">https://etherpad.openstack.org/p/magnum-native-docker-network&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>From &lt;a href="http://dockone.io/article/445">http://dockone.io/article/445&lt;/a>&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>