<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tracing on Feisky</title>
    <link>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in tracing on Feisky</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-cn</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 17:27:47 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://feisky.xyz/tracing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>bcc</title>
      <link>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/bcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Dec 2016 17:27:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/bcc/</guid>
      <description>BPF Compiler Collection (BCC) - Tools for BPF-based Linux IO analysis, networking, monitoring  Website: https://github.com/iovisor/bcc  Basic usage of bcc （tutorial） Install bcc:
echo -e &#39;[iovisor]\nbaseurl=https://repo.iovisor.org/yum/nightly/f23/$basearch\nenabled=1\ngpgcheck=0&#39; | sudo tee /etc/yum.repos.d/iovisor.repo yum install bcc-tools  Now bcc is installed at /usr/share/bcc/tools.
# ls /usr/share/bcc/tools argdist cachestat ext4dist hardirqs offwaketime softirqs tcpconnect vfscount bashreadline cachetop ext4slower killsnoop old solisten tcpconnlat vfsstat biolatency capable filelife llcstat oomkill sslsniff tcplife wakeuptime biosnoop cpudist fileslower mdflush opensnoop stackcount tcpretrans xfsdist biotop dcsnoop filetop memleak pidpersec stacksnoop tcptop xfsslower bitesize dcstat funccount mountsnoop profile statsnoop tplist zfsdist btrfsdist doc funclatency mysqld_qslower runqlat syncsnoop trace zfsslower btrfsslower execsnoop gethostlatency offcputime slabratetop tcpaccept ttysnoop  capable</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sysdig</title>
      <link>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/sysdig/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 17:26:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/sysdig/</guid>
      <description>Tips of sysdig Sysdig captures system calls and other system level events using a linux kernel facility called tracepoints, providing a rich set of real-time, system-level information.
Sysdig &amp;ldquo;packetizes&amp;rdquo; this information, so that you can do things like save it into trace files and easily filter it, a bit like you would do with tcpdump. This makes it very flexible to explore what processes are doing.
Sysdig instruments your physical and virtual machines at the OS level by installing into the Linux kernel and capturing system calls and other OS events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>perf</title>
      <link>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/perf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/perf/</guid>
      <description>perf简介 perf是Linux内核自带的性能分析工具。通过它，应用程序可以利用 PMU，tracepoint 和内核中的特殊计数器来进行性能统</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>systemtap</title>
      <link>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/systemtap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://feisky.xyz/tracing/systemtap/</guid>
      <description>SystemTap是DTrace的Linux实现，它把用户提供的脚本转换为内核模块来执行，用来监测和跟踪内核事件。 安装 注意，较新的内核不支持</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>